Hallelujah!
You may be seated, thank you.
Just as I want to dance, sing and smile, where would I start?
Should I start from smiling?
(Smiling)
Do you see it so genuine?
What next?
That should be the last.
If I dance, I would not be able to sing.
Which song do you want me to sing?
(Singing)
I was listening to that.
(Singing and dancing)
Good Morning, Church!
We try to run but we are still just a baby before the Gospel of Christ.
Baby, like, kindergarten and nursery.
Because when you see what is happening - people are ignorant of the things of the Spirit.
You see them talking about the things of the Spirit, but they don't know what they are talking about.
The case of the Bible is not like that. We have taken the Bible as literature.
Literature is the letter; some say it is Scripture.
Your own scripture seems not to be inspired.
One fact that makes the Word of God unique is the indwelling of the Holy Spirit.
Scripture can just be the letter if it is not inspired by the Spirit.
What are you reading? Which one is your Bible -
the Bible you consider as letter or the one inspired by the Spirit?
That is the question you need to ask yourself.
The Bible demands the state of our heart before reading.
It's not like all sorts of other books.
You cannot hold grudges, pick up the Bible and begin to read.
When you are disturbed in your heart and you are picking up the Bible to read,
you cannot hear from God.
It is not possible.
It is not literature, history or novels.
Literature may not demand the state of your heart.
You may be disturbed and read literature. You may be crying and read literature.
You may hold offence and read literature. You may hold unforgiveness and read literature.
Hatred...
But the Bible is the Scripture inspired by the Spirit and demands the state of your heart.
The question - what is the state of your heart?
Tell you neighbour, What is the state of your heart while reading the Bible?
What is the state of your heart while reading the Bible?
While carrying the Bible, what is the state of your heart?
The Bible demands the state of our heart.
Let me take you to the Book of Psalms 66:18:
"If I had cherished sin in my heart, the Lord would not have listened."
When you have sympathy -
you conceal, keep pain of the past, unforgiveness, hatred, envy, jealousy -
and you are taking the Bible to read,
you are not reading the Bible I know but you are reading literature.
Don't forget, when you open the Bible and read, you are hearing God talk.
Tell your neighbour, "When you open the Bible and read, you are hearing God talk".
"Blessed are the pure in heart, for they shall see God."
Will you be able to hear God?
You cannot.
You will not hear God if you regard sin, keep the pain of the past, unforgiveness, hatred in your heart.
The Holy Bible demands the state of your heart before reading it.
I know this is the first time you are hearing this because it's too elementary, kindergarten.
But these are the things that we abandon and overlook.
Can you imagine where our problem is coming from?
We are facing the biggest challenge in our lives - ignorance of the things of the Spirit.
If I have an unforgiving spirit, pain of the past, envy and jealousy,
I have to get rid of these before opening the Bible
because when you open the Bible and read, you are hearing God talk.
How will you hear from God with envy in your heart?
Our heart is the communication point.
How will you hear from God with envy, jealousy, pain of the past, an unforgiving spirit?
You cannot hear from God because reading the Bible is hearing God talk.
Everyone here, no single one is out of this.
Everybody here.
Who then, is a Christian?
We are all religious people.
Prayer and Bible reading should always go together.
This means we must fill our prayer with Scripture.
Whatever you want to say in your prayer should come from the Scripture.
Not the one - "In the name of Jesus, that my enemy..."
What you say in your prayer, where do you get it from?
Prayer has a language; you must speak its language.
Prayer and Bible reading should always go together.
You must fill your prayer with Scripture - what you have read.
If you want it to be in line with the Holy Ghost, with God, you must fill your prayer with Scripture.
We don't know how to pray; the Holy Ghost helps us in our weakness.
What are we talking about?
We are saying that you have not been filling your prayer with Scripture.
We are saying that you have not been doing the right thing.
We are saying that you are reading the Bible as if you are reading literature.
We are saying that you are reading the Bible as if you are reading history.
This is what we are saying.
Great danger.
I can see why you are having nightmares.
I can see why you complain about how you are doing and how you are feeling.
One fact that makes the Word of God so unique and special
is the indwelling of the Holy Ghost.
The thoughts of the Bible are from the Spirit.
It's not from our father, you or T.B. Joshua.
The language is from men but the thoughts of the Bible are from the Spirit.
Tell your neighbour, "The thoughts of the Bible are from the Spirit and the language is from men".
The SCOAN Sunday Service
What are you saying?
Are you saying what the Holy Spirit is saying?
If the one preaching, teaching, praying, counselling is not in line with the Holy Ghost,
he is merely saying words, talking to the air
because the thoughts of the Bible are from the Spirit and the language is from men.
That is why you will not see me disturbing you with verses of the Bible,
"Open the book of Luke, pray... open the book of this".
It is just reference. The words are directly from the Spirit.
You must develop your relationship with the Holy Ghost by reading your Bible daily without grudges.
To develop your relationship with the Holy Ghost, you must read your Bible with a free spirit.
You must read your Bible with a free spirit.
Tell your neighbour.
If not, you are reading history.
You know these novels - James Hardley Chase and all others.
If the Word dominates your mouth, it will dominate your heart.
If the Word dominates your heart, it will influence your conduct and character.
You keep saying, "Why all this? I'm a Christian! No, no, no!"
because this Word has not influenced your character.
You say, "It is not possible for me! I have tried my best! I don't know why!"
When you are reading a novel - you are reading history!
I like your Bible because it's very small and very neat.
Oh my God. How old is this Bible?
I want to encourage you.
You must read your Bible slowly - because it is the wisdom of God - attentively and repeatedly.
There is no way you can read something slowly, attentively and repeatedly
under tension and pressure - it is not possible.
You can only do that when you are calm, not rough.
You must read your Bible slowly, attentively and repeatedly.
The more you read, the more you will understand about yourself and this God who created you.
Tell your neighbour, "The more you read slowly, attentively, repeatedly,
the more you understand about yourself and this God who created you".
Because you don't understand yourself; everyday you surprise, astonish yourself.
You suddenly wake up in the morning and see blood.
You suddenly wake up in the morning and realise you bedwetted.
You suddenly wake up in the morning and cannot stand up.
You suddenly wake up in the morning and cannot open your mouth.
You suddenly wake up in the morning and they have to carry you to the hospital.
You suddenly wake up in the morning (and start panting).
You don't understand yourself.
When we start praying now, you will start saying, "I have three powers".
By the time they have finished with your deliverance, you will say, "I don't know what I was saying".
This is because you don't understand yourself.
Say, "I don't understand myself".
Again.
"I don't understand myself."
If you don't understand yourself, what will you understand?
Charity begins at home.
Read your Bible slowly, attentively and repeatedly.
The more you read, the more you understand about yourself and this God who created you.
If you don't understand yourself, how will you understand your Creator?
Each time you move to a frightening place, like a beach -
you see the beach being rough - you will say, "God is great!"
When you hear thunder, you say, "God is great!"
You don't understand yourself.
You just live by imagination; you don't know whether you will see tomorrow.
I have seen many of your friends and colleagues -
when you visit their funeral, the stories - oh my God!
If they had known they were about to die, they would have made proper arrangements.
Someone would say, "Hello, we will see each other tomorrow".
The next day you learn that he is in the grave.
Don't forget our lives are static - motionless, stagnant.
Remember, no state of being is as rewarding as living in tune with God.
That is why people like me can be here today.
You know the many efforts people have made to destroy this ministry.
You know the many efforts people have made to silence this ministry.
But GOD refused.
Tell your neighbour, "No state of being is as rewarding as living in tune with God".
You just need to discover whom you are and your real value.
You don't know your value.
Suddenly, you kneel down for someone to pray for you
whereas you are better than the person praying for you.
He would be saying, "I rebuke you, in Jesus' name! I bless you!"
And you don't know that you are supposed to be the one to pray for him.
You are just like that; you don't know about yourself.
You just go down on your knees, "Oga, pray for me!"
Oga will now say, "Jesus Christ!"
Whereas you are supposed to be the one to pray for this oga, and not oga to pray for you.
It is because you don't know whom you are and your real value.
Many who are supposed to be in the palace are on the street.
Many are doing someone else's job.
Many marry someone else's wife or husband.
Discover whom you are and your real value.
Tell your neighbour.
When you find yourself tired and you don't know what to do, you have now turned to a copy.
Suddenly you look at someone, "Ah, I like this attire!" - you wear it.
"I like this business!" - you abandon your business.
"I like going to this country!" - you abandon going to the country you were going to before.
Get interested in God's plan.
I know some of our members who for many years don't have any assignment to do in this church.
All they do is to come on Sundays and worship; they believe so much in their dirty money.
Money is dirty. Where did you get the money?
Out of the money you are bringing, where did you get it from?
You think that this money can pave the way for you. No!
Our elderly women are the ones cleaning the church and the seats for you.
You keep on coming to the church, and after service, they would be the ones to clean the benches.
Get interested in His plans, projects.
God's opinion of yourself and others is very important but you don't know.
What is God's opinion about you?
You cannot know God's opinion about others and about me.
That is why, when you leave from here, you will tell others,
"Ah, this is what happened; this is what the man said!"
You need someone to confirm who T.B. Joshua is to you.
This is why we are being deceived.
Someone needs to tell you, "Yes, he is a man of God; the message is good.
Ah, the hand is shaking! I don't understand that one!"
The SCOAN Sunday Service
No state of being is as rewarding as living in tune with God because our lives are static.
There are many who were millionaires yesterday, but today, they have nothing. They are here.
There are many who were poor yesterday, but today, they are rich.
There are many who had good health yesterday, buy today, they are sick.
Our lives are static - lifeless, unpredictable.
This is not the promise of God. They are new every morning.
Get interested in His plan.
What is God's plan? What is God's project? Are you involved?
You are involved in many projects you are doing. Which one is God's project?
Which of these projects you are involved in is God's project?
In your ministry, wherever you worship, living church -
find one day in a week and join the sanitation department - people cleaning the seats -
to tell the Lord that, "Here I am, tame me, change me.
I want to learn at Your feet, I want to sit at Your feet".
In your ministry.
If you are high over there, come down.
Look at yourself - you are sitting now.
You don't know the person you are sitting with.
Whether he is a millionaire or average.
But you don't mind; you just look for a seat.
But out there, you want to sit where you sit, where your class and status sit.
But here, you see that everyone is just looking for a seat.
You don't mind whether the next person is rich, a housemaid, gardener, cleaner.
You don't mind; you just want to sit and listen to the Word of God.
This is the way it should be.
When you want to work in the house of God too, don't look for a job of your status.
When the doors are opened, everybody wants to sit down;
you don't want to know who sits beside you.
You would be very surprised that the person beside you is a gardener, driver outside.
But out there, you sit with your level, status, and class.
That is the Kingdom of God for you.
Don't forget the Word of God is not literature.
When you are reading the Word of God, you are reading the Holy Spirit, not history.
When you are reading the Bible, you are reading the Holy Ghost.
It demands the state of your heart.
The state of your heart must be at its best to read
because when you open the Bible and read, you are hearing God talk.
The Word of God is a tool in the hands of the Holy Ghost to give you peace, healing.
It is a tool to give you deliverance and salvation.
The Word of God is a tool in the hands of the Holy Ghost.
Use me Lord
As a vessel
As a vessel unto honour
Use me Lord
As a vessel
As a vessel unto honour
Use me Lord
It is time you must work with God's projects.
Get interested in His plan to discover whom you are and your real value.
The ministry where you worship - don't leave it; it is your second home.
Take it as your home.
When you wake up in the morning, you clean your floor, car, window.
You have people doing that for you.
But in the house of God, in a week, you must find a day and join people to clean the floor
and take care of the church premises.
Don't leave this for money.
Money's journey is far; you don't know where it's coming from.
You may be seated.
Be ready to answer my question.
A few minutes.
How have you been reading your Bible in the past?
Thank you, Man of God.
Before understanding your teachings, I was reading my Bible without looking to understand God's heart,
to have the best understanding of God's heart.
I have come to understand that if I want to do so,
the first step is to repent and have a pure heart.
The second step is to be humble because when I am humble, then I can be in the presence of God.
This means, if I am not humble, then it is nothing of importance.
The third part is to be sincere with God.
Thank you. Clap for him.
Thank you.
You have the opportunity to preach the Word of God.
Thank you, Man of God.
You are just preaching the Word of God, not even trying to answer my question directly.
Yes.
Clap for him.
Thank you, Man of God.
Thank you.
Ok, can somebody tell us - what are you going to do with this message?
From now on I will read my Bible slowly, attentively, repeatedly, and I will be in tune with God's Word.
How will you be in tune with God's Word?
I will not hold grudges, offence, and envy towards anybody.
Thank you. Did you listen to that?
I will be pure in my heart.
That is, read the Bible with forgiveness.
Tell your neighbour.
Read the Bible with forgiveness.
I can't hear you.
Again.
Read the Bible with forgiveness.
The reading of the Bible demands for the state of your heart, a free spirit.
Thank you. Clap for him.
Any other? Come on.
I must be honest.
Before now, I have not been reading the Bible in accordance with the teachings of today.
The teachings of today have enlightened me.
There are certain things I have learned today that I must apply in the process of reading the Bible
so that I can receive pure communication with God
because reading the Bible is communication with God.
In line with His Word - as you have said - it will make us get inspiration from God to do His work.
Clap for him. Thank you.
Thank you very much. Thank you, sir.
Honestly, let me confess.
In the past, I wanted to cover more pages of the Bible.
For instance, if I took the book of Esther, I wanted to read all.
So I read it, just as I would read other books.
But because of the message this morning, I will take my time
and read the Bible slowly, attentively, and repeatedly.
The second lesson is that in my church, I didn't use to work there.
But because of this message, I will visit my church and work there.
Clap for him. I am happy you mentioned that.
You need to work there.
Now that you have decided to look for an assignment God wants for you to do in the church,
how will you approach this?
I used to occupy myself with the work I do, but because of the message I heard this morning,
I will make time within a week.
I said, how will you approach this. In what way will you approach what you want to do in the church?
I will now sit, restructure my time, take a day within the week.
Who owns your time?
God.
You want to wrestle time with God?
No, please.
This is what you are saying.
So, I am asking you how you will approach this.
I will take a day to visit the church and get involved in any work which is going on.
Don't go and meet your leader, pastor, founder, that you want to work in the church; that is pride.
Your leader or pastor should not choose what to do for you.
You know where your shortcoming and weakness lie.
And the weakness of everyone here is pride.
We need to humble ourselves.
We are too proud, that is why we believe so much in money.
Money answers everything.That is the voice of pride.
Go and join people in the church, work in the department where humility can come,
where you can be humble.
Ok? That is the area you should look into.
Thank you, Man of God. Thank you so much.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Did you listen to that?
Pride is our problem. That is why we believe so much in money.
Tell your neighbour, "Pride is our problem, that is why we believe so much in money".
There is nothing money cannot do for you.
You believe money can stop you from coming to church.
If money wants you to come to church, you will come.
If money does not want you to come to church, you will not come.
If money wants you to fall sick, you will fall sick.
If money wants you to be happy, you will be happy.
Wherever money asks you to go to, you will go.
When you speak, one can hear the voice of money.
When you walk, one can see the traces of money.
Even your dress...
That will give you an opportunity and access to know more about your ministry
when you become part of the working staff.
Don't go and meet your general overseer that you want to work.
What do you want him to say?
There are many departments in your ministry.
It is not the Spirit that cleans the floor
and it is not the Spirit that will pick up the plastics and everything.
Look at - camera, please come forward and capture the plastics.
There are thousands of them!
Someone will move round to pick them.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
A lot. Continue to capture them. You will see a lot.
Not only one. Move around.
I will give you two minutes. Can you see? All of these have been abandoned.
By the time we say the grace, they will abandon everything.
Are you giving them to drink it or to go and sell them?
Church is a family; the ministry of God is a family.
That is why in the olden days, 99% of ministries were called family church.
But today, the opposite is the case.
You clean your windows at home
but someone else will clean the windows in your church.
You sweep the floor in your home.
In your church, someone else will sweep the floor.
Get interested in His plan.
Thank you, Man of God.
What I have learned today is that I should let the Word of God dominate my heart,
and when it dominates my heart, it will dominate my mouth and influence my character.
Through reading the Bible and continuous meditation, it will dominate my heart.
And it must be read with forgiveness, a free spirit.
You must also use the Word you are reading in your prayer.
Thank you, brother. God bless you.
You can give it to our mummy here.
According to the teachings of the prophet this morning, I have learned
that we have to read our Bible slowly, repeatedly, and attentively.
I was not doing that; I would read my Bible whenever I wanted to.
I didn't pray according to the Scripture.
I would read from Monday to Thursday and finish the Bible as if I am reading a novel.
But today, I have learned that I have to read it according to the three points he described.
I should also have interest in God's project, which I do not have because I am a church goer.
I go to church, sit down, and go back home as soon as the church service finishes.
Clap for her. Did you listen to that?
She is educating us.
She is a church goer and would go home immediately after the church service finishes,
believing that her tithes and offerings (are enough).
What kind of...?
Many times, they would ask, "Those who know how to do certain things in church, join us".
But I would just slip away and go.
Tell us more; we want to learn.
So, it's as if the Prophet was talking to me directly; I was touched.
I have to direct myself and not wait for my elders in church to tell me what to do.
Let me just join any group I can.
Join the group that will reshape your character.
Don't join a group because those of your status and class are joining it.
Join a group of people you have nothing to do with out there.
Have something to do with them in the church.
People you don't have anything to do with.
Look for the group they belong to and join it.
People that are below you, your class - join that group in the church to work in.
We should not carry the association we have out there into the church.
This is what is affecting churches today.
We take the association we have outside and bring it into the church.
When you see the group of people in the church, they are of the same association, class out there.
That will not help us.
To help our character, we need someone we can learn from -
someone who has what we do not have, not someone who has what we have.
You would have nothing to learn from them.
You are because I am; I am because you are.
Where you are weak, I am strong; where you are strong, I am weak.
Thank you.
I thank God for this opportunity.
I have always heard that we must forgive others, and not hold grudges while praying.
But most times, I pray holding grudges and unforgiveness,
believing that God would show me mercy.
But I thank God for this privilege that the man of God has emphasised the need to pray only
when you spirit is in tune with God.
Thank you, Man of God.
This working in the house of God - so there is an area we need to add.
When you are going, you have to take your children along.
They must join you.
Thank you, sir.
I remember, in those days - blessed memory of my mum -
when my mum was going to church on Saturday and I was not going to school,
she would make sure I ate the food in the afternoon in the church
because she had a duty to perform in the church.
Because of food, I had to follow.
She would carry the food and say, "Meet me".
I used to play football but I had to cancel it and follow her because I needed to eat.
Our young people, whatever they need, whatever we need to do to bring them close -
we have to do every proper thing to bring them close.
Thank you, sir.
...to entice them and bring them to God.
So that when they are mature, they will understand what you were trying to do for them.
But at a certain age, we have to use our human effort to drag them close to God.
Thank you.
Like I have said, make sure you join people that are below you;
the department they belong to - join that department.
Don't go to the church and join your class out there, what they are doing in the church.
Thank you, madam. God bless you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I learnt that my prayers must be filled with what I studied in the Bible.
If I read the Bible by that means, any time I pray,
the Holy Spirit would direct me to a particular part of the Bible.
because the Bible has a Scripture for every circumstance of life.
And we can't read it just like we read our poems.
If you read it with the guidance of the Holy Spirit, any time you are praying about an issue,
the Holy Spirit will direct you to a particular Scripture that you need to use to sort an issue out.
That is what I have learnt.
Secondly, I have learned to be concerned with God's projects.
The more you concern yourself with God's projects, the more God will be concerned with your projects.
Thank you. The world is demanding so much but what we are demanding is in the Bible.
Like what I was saying - in those days, when I was very little, I used to follow my mummy.
My mummy was one of the people that used to sweep the floor and clean the seats of the church.
Anytime she was cleaning the seats and sweeping the floor, her mouth would be saying something.
I don't know what she was saying.
I realised she would be murmuring and talking.
One day, I said, "Mummy, what are you saying? You would be talking when you are cleaning".
She said, "Ah, I am telling God, 'As I am cleaning Your house, clean my life'".
My mum would clean the floor and seats and she would be going.
Sometimes after she had talked and talked, she would begin to sing praise.
Then, I would say, "Mummy, what do you normally say because when I talk to you,
you would do not reply me. You keep talking to yourself. We don't know what you are saying".
She said, "Ah, I am telling God, 'As I am cleaning Your house, cleanse my life, my future,
my career and my children'".
I think I am one of the people God has given to.
Yes.
She said, "As am cleaning Your house, sweeping the floor, clean my family, future, and children".
Please, get interested in God's plan.
Thank you.
Overflow Congregation
It is time to pray.
You don't have time to pray, whereas prayer should be part of your way of life.
Whenever you are in the church, whatever you are doing at that moment,
keep on praying.
Whatever has come into your heart to do, God will now enlarge your coast.
You find yourself becoming so abundant in what you are doing.
I think this message today is a Spirit-filled message for all of us in the church.
Thank you.
I am guilty of all of it.
I go to church with pride,
and I feel giving my dirty money is what it is all about when worshipping God.
Clap for my brother.
Did you listen to that?
Can you see humility?
He said, we go to church with pride, give our dirty money, and say we are supporting the church.
If you are supporting your church with money, what is the position of that church now?
Man of God, this is a message my pastor has always been talking about.
That we should try to do something in the house of God, and it would bless us and our families.
This message - if I have my way - I would love it to be preached in my church
so that people would know what it means to worship God.
We should not be church goers.
Did you listen to that?
If you do something in the house of God with all your heart,
you are doing it for your generation and for your family.
I told you about the case with my mum.
In those days, when I was little, I would follow my mum.
Mummy was like forcing me with food.
Mummy would be murmuring (whilst cleaning), and later she would start singing.
I would say, "Mummy!" She would not be answering me.
I would ask, "What are you saying? Anytime you are cleaning the benches,
sweeping the floor, what do you usually say? You are always busy murmuring.
I would always see your mouth moving".
She would say, "Ah, what I am saying, my little one - God should clean my life, my children.
'I am cleaning Your house, Lord, clean...'".
But today, I can see indeed...
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Go to the church and join those who are not of your class,
where you become a stranger among them. It is to humble you.
This is what God wants.
Thank you, sir, for your education.
Thank you, Man of God.
Thank you. Did you listen to our brother?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
There are many things you can do.
There are many departments to join.
If we say we are supporting our church, what is the position of the church today in the world?
I am really touched with today's message.
I am a person that keeps grudges.
I have been holding a grudge before coming to this place.
With the grudge I am holding, if I had not heard your message,
and read my Bible, I would have just wasted my time.
Before coming here, my father slapped me for no reason, and the grudge is in my heart.
Because of what you have just preached, I have to leave that grudge
and develop the habit of doing away with grudge,
so that the indwelling Spirit of God will come to me.
If I don't do that, the Spirit of God will not come to me.
And I cannot read the Bible slowly, attentively, and repeatedly...
...when you are disturbed.
Clap for him.
So I am very happy for receiving this message.
I have to forgive my father so that I can move forward.
Did you listen to that?
You say, you want people to do good all the time
and you don't know that this life is two-sided - good and bad.
You should be expecting bad, good, bad, good.
You need more of these challenges to strengthen you to look proper and focused.
You need more of slap, persecution.
You have not yet arrived.
This is the time you should be expecting persecution.
People will embarrass you.
That will help you to give yourself to prayer.
The more you are embarrassed, the more you give yourself to prayer.
I told you the last time that our troubles help us to maintain our union with God.
I am happy to hear from my father here, that he was unjustly slapped.
I think it's good for us, for our strength.
Most especially for those of us that are striving to get to a certain position
and those of us that are yearning to grow in God.
We should be expecting this.
Take your time to read and study the life of T.B. Joshua - my antecedents.
When you look at my antecedents,
you will see that I have more degree in persecution than praise.
I am a professor when it comes to persecution but I am just a first degree holder in praise.
But I am not expecting praise.
I am not expecting praise because my reward is over there.
Thank you. I am happy with this message.
When you leave from here today, no matter how big or little your ministry is..
Some of us are coming from a very small church.
It is good! It is not the size of the ministry that determines its strength.
The strength of a ministry is not in its large population, branches all over
or being the biggest church in the world; the strength does not lie there.
You can see just two members in a church
that is more connected to God than the biggest or largest church.
The strength of the ministry is the relationship of the ministry to God;
it is not the population or crowd, fame or popularity.
That is not the strength of the ministry.
Anything can attract a crowd.
People in the world today go by feelings - what they see and hear.
So, even if your ministry is litle - just a few members - that is good for you.
Join them and help them in whatever they are cleaning in the church.
Find time one day in a week and do it.
Don't meet your general overseer.
Just meet the department concerned and tell them, "Yes, I want to join".
With all your heart.
That will be the day of your fasting.
You can choose that as a day of fasting.
When you are going there with fasting, your children too have to follow you,
just like my mummy was carrying me all the time.
See me today.
The SCOAN Sunday Service